module.exports = [
  {
    question: "Name of Harry Potter's Father",
    options: ['Severus Snape', 'Gandalf', 'Voldemort', 'James Potter'],
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Name of Harry Potter's owl",
    options: ['Hedwig', 'Fluffy', 'Padfoot', 'Norbert'],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Name Draco Malfoy's Dad.",
    options: [
      'Narcissa Malfoy',
      'John Malfoy',
      'Lucius Malfoy',
      'James Malfoy',
    ],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Name of Lord Voldemort's loyal snake",
    options: ['Padfoot', 'Norbert', 'Fang', 'Nagini'],
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: 'The `Killing Curse` spell of Voldemort',
    options: [
      'Expecto patronum',
      'Avada Kedavra',
      'Wingardium Leviosa',
      'Expelliarmus',
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the spell used for disarming people?',
    options: [
      'Expecto patronum',
      'Avada Kedavra',
      'Wingardium Leviosa',
      'Expelliarmus',
    ],
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Harry Potter's godfather?",
    options: ['Voldemort', 'Hagrid', 'Tommy Angelo', 'Sirius Black'],
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What was Ron's pet name?",
    options: ['Scrabbers', 'Norbert', 'Fang', 'Hedwig'],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: 'Who did Draco Malfoy called Mudblood?',
    options: ['Hermione', 'Ron Weasley', 'Harry Potter', 'Ginny'],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: 'Who married Harry Potter?',
    options: ['Hermione', 'Luna Lovegood', 'Ginny Weasely', 'Cho Chang'],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: 'Where did exactly Harry meet Tom Riddle for the first time?',
    options: [
      'Hogwarts',
      'Chamber of Secrets',
      'Little Hangleton',
      "Godric's Hollow",
    ],
    answer: 2,
  },
];
